Every home's a secret, every shadow knows my fate.
Our gateways without hinges, it smiles upon them.
I woke up to something interesting.
You know, I've probably been about,
for maybe it's been about a month
that I've been trying to apologize for having that person.
Listen, I have a very adverse,
like a lot of my audience is adversarial towards me.
It's kind of like, you know,
I just call them trolls or whatever, some of them.
consider kind of friends, some of them, more than others, but some were adversarial and
they're in Belfast. So nice, Lisa. Beautiful. 1046 in Belfast. PM. Awesome. Scotland? Is that
Scotland? Wonderful to see you, Lisa. Thank you for being here. But so let's just, but maybe I
just didn't say it at the right time in the right place with the right title of my stream.
So I'm sure people will be watching this to see what I'm gonna say about it
You know whether they like me or not, but I'll give my side of
My view and it's like because sometimes we can look at it's Northern Ireland. Okay, great
Sometimes we can look we can actually like, you know
Come to understanding if we like actually listen to people. That's what I try to do. You know, I'm very hey reality Nancy
You can't save a date good. Oh have fun in your day. Yeah
well I'm just gonna do a little expose I'm like you know what I should have done
to begin with but again I don't know if people understand like the people some of the people
that were sending this evidence thank you so much Lisa I appreciate that so much thank you so so much
I love you um unfortunately it was like the wrong the wrong person that it happened with but
you know um if you've got if you have people especially the people that were attacking you
I don't know about you, but I I don't like to be told what to do
And I know I know people like that maybe some people take advantage of that because you can like
And maybe use reverse psychology on me
Say don't do this and I'll do it. No, um, but um
You the you look beat us. I'm you a while ago. Well, you know, I'm beat and I have you know
We've had our differences and I don't I don't think she cares much for me anymore, but um, yeah, but I appreciate
Appreciate you so her still being here
And, but anyway, so when I had all these, you know,
it was basically what I used it as, you know,
I basically, you know, maybe Brandon was using me
or whatever, but I was using him.
And maybe I, and maybe the wrong person to use,
maybe it was a little bit too strong of a,
of a annoyance, not too strong.
I mean, it's like, you know, I don't know.
But I got into, I got into, I got into it with it.
And, but then it, it spiraled into,
a nightmare, right?
Yeah, it's sad, but, you know,
hey, at the end of the day,
you know I'm a forgiving person,
that's my problem, is that,
and it's also, you know,
there's so many accusations and things
thrown around the community,
but so I'm going to slow to react to it,
but then, also, like, yeah,
I mean, it was like, people like beat in Sam and,
that were like, you know,
I didn't care that they got mad.
I mean, I like, I thought I irritated people
and I liked irritating some of the people.
And I didn't like, and some of the people I didn't,
it was too strong of a thing to use.
And maybe not right to do that, but,
and maybe I didn't watch the evidence or whatever close enough
because I was sent by people, some people,
I am definitely ops with already, but okay, let's go over.
what I've got in my discord because the discord, you know stuff was actually and also I will say this
It's like I lost access to my discord or I would have like maybe come around back to this earlier
I lost access to it when I when I read
Format on my computer and reinstall windows and stuff. I couldn't get back into my discord
So I've been a new discord, but I was able to get into my old discord now
Just you know someone you someone who even got me in there and so I see all these videos now
And so we can you like with people or yeah
Yeah, you know you weren't here when people were fighting. Yeah, it wasn't it wasn't too bad of a fighting here
It's just like a lot of like behind-the-scenes stuff and another shows and stuff
And it's just like a really it really hurt some relationships and I feel really bad that if I if I
But and I really want to apologize if I if some people because I
Stook stood up for him that day that also stood up for him and and then you know, I guess it is my fault
And I'm sorry, you know, I'm sorry that I
I ever stood up for this piece of human waste
who fucking turned on everybody.
And I don't know, maybe at the end of the day,
maybe some terrible mental problems
and it needs to be in a padded room this guy, okay?
But let's do my discord, okay?
So my discord, I've got these videos, okay?
I've got everything.
Okay, I said I looked at it. It's everything's almost everything, but we also have um, oh first I'm gonna actually play
I'm great. I'm grateful and grateful be your student. You know I annex who also, you know
has a soft heart for people and
You know, I think that she was gonna went to maybe a
school in that in that New Mexico at one time and
You know and and he comes off as like a little bit like a
You know, he can fool you, because he has a little innocent look in a certain way.
I mean, the mask falls pretty easy with him, and then it's like, you're like, uh-oh, it's too late.
I don't know. All I can say is I'm sorry, but it's like, you know, if I'm not forgiven by people,
forgiveness is not something for me to ask for, it's something for people to freely give.
And so, you can accept my apology or not, you know?
Like, there's no more words than that, I can say, you know, I regret it, I made a mistake,
you know.
Is it, did I do anything unforgivable?
I don't really think so, because we all have free will, and we all make mistakes.
Anyone's perfect, let me know.
And then, you know, you can throw the first stone at me, right?
So let's go to my Discord.
Okay.
So here's my Discord.
Actually, I'm not gonna, I'm gonna be careful about a joke.
I don't want to like, dox anybody or anything,
but okay, so let me go into my Koto Psyche Discord.
Okay, let me scroll up to about a couple of months ago.
I was the nightmare started, and we can see.
Actually careful, there might be some immunity.
I'm not sure about showing this of him, you know.
There it is, something about his butt or something like that.
But let's see.
Because we got a lot of stuff in here. Okay, so this is oh my god. Oh my god. Okay
There are some crazy scary things. Okay, so okay, so this must be okay. So right here was before that all
Then here's when the nightmare started. So let's get to okay
I'm gonna do the Ion X video first is Ion X will lay out kind of what he has done
I consider myself wishy-washy
No, but like I said, I was using it to kind of like take care of my ops and stuff like that because it's like, you know
You know how people will like, oh, I mean, he's the worst opp, right?
But now it's like, am I wishy-washy?
Hey, in some things, I'm a little bit hesitant to jump on the hate train with some things.
Okay, let me let me be the conductor of this hate train. Okay, but let me see YouTube
I'll get to Ion X's video and she will explain a lot of stuff happening behind the scenes with him that you guys don't know about
Okay, there's more stuff happening than you think a lot of stuff was happening. Okay behind the scenes and
You know, I don't have any X to grind against anyone particularly except for him. Okay despite anything
I understand I made a mistake and that led to bad consequences for me and you know
I'm gonna have to deal with those consequences, but if I can I'm going to
try to redeem myself in a little bit if I can but
Because I don't really don't think I've done something that unforgivable, but
That's up for every individual person aside and not for me to decide
Because we all have free will right?
Okay, so this is um, this is an ex's video that she just did and
This will explain a lot about what's happening behind the scenes that you might not know about okay
And I'll get to your questions too. Okay, but here we go. Oh my gosh
okay, so this is this is a let's watch this video together and
Come get your popcorn hold my hand by looking them slipknot. Hey me Mason. Yeah, I sometimes
What's that song duality that's duality? I like duality, okay?
Okay, so here's uh, let's everyone listen to uh
Yeah, I know we'd be an iron off on me. Who knows who knows what will happen, but you know
She does not like me very much. I probably said things
and done things that
Not necessarily on purpose, but here here we go. Is it up do you see it? No, no here. There you go
with this guy I mean he was blowing her up about gamble and I guess she gave him
a chance and she asked me and somebody else to help support him and she felt
bad for this idiot
but he turned on her
And it didn't make sense why he turned on her just because she was talking to
Salmon or something and he said she's talking to the ops. I will show our
Converse conversation this guy goes crazy. Look what he said here fuck Alex
I did a live about her this morning and it was a fake
Dono he makes fake dono alerts he and everybody even called him out for the fake donos
Alex did not give him a thousand dollars, and then he was on panel saying oh, she gave me four thousand this guy is a liar
He was trying to control
Psyche telling him not to play the music or I mean, I don't know who he thinks he is Psyche has a real
You know channel this guy it's all fake
Thank you, Gamble, for letting me know about, you know, all those bots are fake, and I mean,
this guy is crazy. I gave him chance after chance, but here he has fuck Alex after everything she
did for him. So everything he said about Gamble is our lies. The picture he keeps posting of Gamble
in the water, that was some kind of party going on, and there was a kid in the water.
But I don't even know why the kid was there, but he wasn't showing his ass
He had a string thing whatever he was joking around and it was a video and
So anyway, if I got excited alive about her this morning
Yeah, lie because Alex did not give him a thousand dollars
I donated twenty five dollars to her a couple years ago because she had a she did a great video. It was alive
It was interesting
She never asked, I just donate sometimes when I like something, but I gave her the 25 and
she thanked me and that was it and that was all. She never took advantage of me or anything and
this guy is lying about her and he went nuts and me like an idiot fell for it.
And so I don't know so then anyway Alex was mad, but look at this
Look, you know, he's obsessed. This is me. Okay, this is me and he's using an old fat pic
That's what a piece of shit he is
Fuck elder. I don't even care about that fag. Everybody's a fag to you
I mean you have a problem with everybody you have mental issues Brandon and they even docks your address error on
Where you're at? I'm glad I don't
Give strangers my real number up. You know I use a text number
And so, this is ridiculous, but anyway, he was posting Clumsy's little boy's picture.
He says, well, he's in his 20th now.
It doesn't matter.
You still posted a kid's picture, and I recorded that call, because he said, what was it?
He said, I asked him, and Clumsy was there.
You could hear him.
He put him on panel, but you couldn't see him.
And I asked him, where did you get the picture?
Well, I found it online.
And this guy's a piece of shit, doxing kids.
And he's lying because I remember I shared a video of him hitting on the little girl
And that was from KK's live and I don't know why Alex missed that because she I guess you try to give him a chance
But he's crazy and then and then he got arrested. He did attack a dog
I'll go ahead and post that I did get the video and he was trying to tell me. Oh, whatever they sent you is is
What was it there? They were hacking your computer. So it doesn't work. He's paranoid. He's crazy
But look at this and you know, these are our techs. He's crazy 500 texts
It was you calling me stalking me on psyches
Look at this and he's going off about teller BSR. He has an issue with him, too
And I was telling him yeah, I think that's a weird guy because he thought it was somebody else
So that's a telewisely calling you. What business is it of yours? Okay. I have a friend on there and you're stalking me too
You know, this is crazy. Okay. I mean, this is come this is me. Okay. This was me on FaceTime
Well, actually that was from like a year and a half ago. I do FaceTime psyche saw me
So I asked you that was him and you said no see he's asking me questions about people he sees he's paranoid
So he's got a problem with the Tyler
That goes by BSR
You know, I lost a few a few people on here even the Kate Barry
Because Barry warned me and he was so mad at me and you know
We blocked each other over Brandon and a lot of people have been pissed off and I'm done with this
Crystal I appreciate you telling me the truth about this guy and I wasn't listening now
I see that everything is true about this weirdo guy and he's obsessed with clumsy. He's pissed off at psyche
He's obsessed with gamble
There's no proof of Gamble doing anything to a kid. They said he groomed a kid named Daniel, meaning
he had him on his panel when he had DX, but that was years ago when he was young and
it wasn't any, I wouldn't even call that grooming. It was just a kid that joined the panel and
Him and a lot of people were talking to him. That's all it was. It wasn't anything weird
So anyway, is it Tyler or not? See, look, I don't know another person he has an issue with. And then look, the pussy psyche made it private. I hate that fact. I mean, this guy's crazy.
If I have to, I'll show the rest of our text and especially him going nuts on Alex talking to an op or whatever. And, you know, and I don't know, that was stupid. And we pretty much turned on her, I guess.
But I don't want shit to do with this guy.
You guys all warned me about him.
I should have listened.
And he's a batshit crazy guy with bots.
He doesn't even have real people in his chats.
He's crazy.
He's making up, like he even said that somebody told him
to go unalive somebody.
Where's the proof?
Because I'll go ahead and do a recording of our entire text
because nothing like that was said.
He never shows proof.
He runs his mouth.
Alex did not donate a thousand or four thousand dollars and and me like an idiot shared that because I believed it until people
Showed what exactly he was doing and you can tell those donors are alert and you can see that in his face because he's like
Oh, oh, oh, I got that thousand dollar. It was just so fake
So yeah, this is it so and this is what I said to him and he tried to call me
Okay, that's not a 500 text. The guy is crazy
And I didn't know that sometimes when I was when he'd call me at my text now number when he'd call me that
he was a
Live and without my permission. He was I didn't even know that I was be I was he was showing our
Conversation or on live on his lives. I'm sorry. I just woke up. I'm so mad
I shouldn't have fallen for this and you guys were pissed off at me. I am so sorry
Um, and I didn't listen to you guys about about this idiot
Um, people blocked me uh people i've been cool with and every one of them is
Saying it was because uh that i'm talking to this pedo
He is a pedo. Why is he getting on monkey app when he knows that's for kids?
Trying to fake it like oh, you should be off the internet when he's hitting on these kids
And I'll go ahead and post them those videos if I have to the only thing he has it's an old fat pick of me from
2016 and he's an asshole. It's like I was thinking about it's like he is so shady
He's so shady
You know that oh, I'm sorry. I was distracted by the text. I thought it was at this guy
But no, it's going to my phone because I have my regular phone number
Which starts with the 281 so and the other number is is a text now
So, um, yeah, I'm just blown away that this guy is psycho and in gamble gamble gamble
And then he stalks me like everywhere I go. He's watching me and then he goes nuts and
I don't appreciate him, you know using me for content while he's talking to me and most times I didn't even know
That he was live and we're talking about this bullshit or bashing somebody or always somebody and
You know, that's illegal for him to do. He just doesn't have anybody though and all those bots in his chat
Gamble was right, you know and me like an idiot didn't listen. I listened to him
You'll see all this hate and about how he hates Alex and she's a piece of shit
And he didn't want to talk to her when she was helping him he turns on everybody this guy is psycho and
Yeah, they everybody has his information
You know, I didn't post this information
But I will call in because from what somebody said is he's got some problems over there now, but Kirkie for for
Stocking or whatever and he did hit the dog. He attacked the dog. He was
Going crazy and that's a crazy branding that we see there was no drugs or anything
He tried to say that gamble gamble's friend was with him
And gave him a drug or it didn't make any sense because that's a crazy person that we see lately
That's how he behaves. He's insane and he needs mental help
But these were our recent texts and I'll go ahead and screen record all the rest of them and you'll see how crazy he sounds
So Brandon stop stalking us
Stop looking for this Tyler guy. You're going after all these people
And you were banned on psyches and I didn't even know that you were on there trying to start crap with him and trying to tell him how to run his channel.
When you don't even have anything going on in yours all your whole channel is all fake and you're talking to yourself and gaming.
I mean, this is ridiculous guys.
So I'm going to go ahead and post record the rest because he's completely crazy.
And I am going to go ahead and make a report because this guy is completely nuts.
And he went crazy when I was on Crystal's panel asking for that video because it wouldn't open and he went completely nuts on me
Brandon you're crazy. Alex was trying to help you
She gave you a chance and she believed your story about Gamble because she wasn't she wasn't sure though
But you're you have guys look up his background
You have has anybody checked his background about what he does it with these kids?
But yeah, I'm gonna go ahead and show that other video too when he's hitting up on the little girl
Who's 13 8th grade and she's drinking and he's encouraging her to drink and saying he's drinking
that was on the monkey monkey app and
Now people are clipping or they're posting clips of him hitting on other kids
This guy is sick
So Brandon leave me alone
I don't want anything to do with you because I will call the police over there and
Let them know what you're doing dumbass because I record everything online
Okay, and you need to leave me alone, and I think that was you trying to message my
Text now just now when you're blocked, but everything is recorded. Okay dumbass
Okay, okay
Let me get into the discord. Okay, let me see. Oh my god
Okay, let's get to that good stuff. Okay, here we go ready guys. Okay, that was pretty good. Okay, let's see. Okay, here we go. I'm going to actually download these and then start to play them on my show. Here we go. So I don't, I don't show my discord. Here we go.
I promise you, I'm not an alcoholic.
I'm gonna be honest, I'm not even in high school yet.
I drink like this.
I'm going into high school.
When I'm in high school?
You could drink more than me.
I would already be able to.
When I'm in eighth grade, trust me, I was bringing shit to school.
I hate when people call me an alcoholic.
Take a shot.
Dude.
Okay.
There we go.
I'm sorry, I didn't.
Look at these some of them. I thought we're from Tony. Okay. Okay. Let's continue
Is that the same one? Let's oh, there's I guess this is a
Hi, Rudy. This is another one of that
Okay, it's saved
Hold on. Let me see if it's a different. Thank you. Thank you. Okay. Looks like the same same video
Okay, so let me see if there's another I know I think there's like a 20 minute one. Yeah. Oh, here we go
Let me make sure again
Okay, I want to see this check this out
What a print what a predator bro
What a predator
go have a baby bro like I said bro go have a baby what else um let's see and
he got in the discord started to post a bunch of shit but those are all gone
hold on um do I have the oh here we go here's another one if I am I have to if
I I should I should be right right I should have I can watch these here
I was hoping there was a 20 minute video
because that's, I guess, the coup de gras.
Okay, here, I'm gonna try to add this person
to my, back to my new discourse.
Let me just run them.
Oh, going friend request.
Okay, let's see, no, no.
Oh, it's the wrong person.
Okay, let's see.
If anybody has a 20 minute, oh, here it is, I found it.
Okay, okay, we're gonna watch it. I found the video. Okay, here we go guys
And we're gonna watch the full thing here we go and viewer discretion is biased. Thank you 2020. I know well
I feel pretty stupid
I'm paying the consequences, but this is the dude that probably should be
Facing these consequences. Here we go
trigger warning I want gamble to get married bro and have a daughter dude. I want you to bro
There's my then you'll see what a PDF is bro. I'll show you
I'm not an alcoholic. I'm gonna be honest. I'm not even in high school yet. I drink like this. I'm going into ice
When I'm in high school more than me I would already be all fucked up when I'm
I'm in the highest eighth grade, trust me.
I was bringing shit to school.
No, I hate when people call me an alcoholic.
Take a shot.
Dude.
Prove it, prove it.
I just-
That's a child, that's a child, that's a child,
that's a child, that's a child, that's a child.
She's 15.
Exactly bro, and this dude Michelle Ashley is a minor. I don't even know who Ashley is bro. That's a big profile
We're all going van Ashley words Ashley in the chat, bro. All right, Ashley. Yes, man, bro
I'm glad my vibe is how this bro. I hope you
Hello, who are you? Oh, so you're actually is this Ashley? Is this?
Who are you then?
What the hell?
Chris Hansen
You
No, I'm not recording you bro. I'm not recording you. I'm not recording you. I didn't record you bro
That's just your cat all day today. This is and I got a girlfriend, bro
You're fucking daddy bro in your fucking dad's house, bro
This dude's girlfriend. This dude's girlfriend doesn't even fucking live nowhere near him, bro
Look the pussy's calling me dude. Hey, what's up pussy?
Hey, what's up bitch fuck up watch what I'm in Florida you fucking pussy fuck funny thing bro a chick literally said a
chick lied about getting raped with him too, bro
Hello
Hey, what's up coward you didn't do shit shut your fucking mouth, bro. Oh fuck. What's going on coward? What?
Yeah, what?
I'm gonna beat you dad at this time dude
And I'm gonna fucking leave you, you fucking delusional
What you just did, you're fucked
Congrats
Kill yourself bro, kill yourself
No, look at who's the one bro
Who are the people that got me almost put in prison bro
For the rest of my life and caused me this pain bro
Fuck!
Yeah!
Fuck you!
Fuck yeah!
I'll be motherfuckers burn bro!
I'll be drop a nuclear bomb on all you motherfuckers, bro.
Fucking die, bitch.
I'll be your motherfuckers die.
It's oh, I great, oh, I great you.
Oh, he great me, dude.
And then she's saying, oh, I said,
I didn't say you great me.
I said that you, she said this,
I have her on recording saying this.
She said that I didn't say you great me.
I said that you, uh, come inside me unconcentrally.
Got her clan B because she said you raped her.
Ah!
You're a fucking idiot, dude. That's what she said. She tried saying that. She said that I that I come dinner unconsensually, bro
Fuck you pussy. You live with your fucking dad bitch
Fuck pussy
Fuck you, bro
Fuck your bitch ass, bro. You're a pussy, dude. Fuck you. I'm so fucked in the head, dude
I've already so much shit has already almost happened to me, bro
Where I've almost been sent to prison for the rest of my life, bro for shit. I didn't do dude
Um, or I felt that way, bro, or I felt I felt in a way bro where we're trying to do that
Fuck you bitches, bro. Fuck you motherfuckers that do that shit, bro
That have tried to set me up bro try to fucking get me in trouble dude or try to from everything bro
I'm not even talking about just this dude
I'm talking about everything bro all the people that have tried to lie on me or try to set me up dude
Get me killed get me fired bro make me be homeless bro all that shit
DO SOMETHING, MOTHERFUCKER! I WANT YOU TO DO SOMETHING, BITCH!
Hey, it's gonna get worse. It's always gonna get worse.
DO SOMETHING, PUSSY!
He's crying.
What, coward?
It's gonna get worse.
SHUT UP, PUSSY! YOU AIN'T GONNA DO SHIT!
DO SOMETHING, MOTHERFUCKER!
DO SOMETHING, BITCH!
DO SOMETHING!
Do something motherfucker. I'm a member. I can't remember what the fuck I was it's cuz of alcohol alcoholic, bro
You know what bro, I hope somebody really does fucking rape you bitch and fucking kills you bitch
Fuck you. I hope that bitch really does get raked bro and get, I hope somebody fucking rapes her and shoots her in the back of the fucking head bitch, rapes her in the fucking ass, and boom bro, blasts her in the back of the motherfucking head bitch.
Fuck you, cock. Dumb bitch. You fucking dumb bitch. Fuck you. They're trying to make me have a mental breakdown bro. Fuck you bitch. Fuck you.
Well, you don't do shit, bitch. It's that sit on your fucking ass, bro, and take pills like a fucking junkie bitch
Fuck you, bro
Oh, well, it's obviously bullshit. So shut the fuck up. Post it pussy. Post it
Post it post it post it coward
Shut up pussy. You're a bitch dude. Shut the fuck up, bro. Shut fuck you, bro
Shut up. You're a bitch. Fuck you, dude
Fucking pussy ass bitch. Yeah, I'm a fucking pussy dude. I'm gonna fuck her soft as fuck, dude
Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck
Shut your fucking mouth, bro
Shut the fuck up
She told the cops that I raped her dude
You did
I don't know guns, it's faith in me
But you put a gun to my head when you said that shit
You don't remember that?
Tell him I want to rape you
You motherfuckers!
I don't give a fuck, I'll just boss myself, how about that bro?
I'm gonna beat you, that is just not good
And I'm gonna fucking rape you
Fucking die!
Okay, did you know, I'm contacting you
Contact me, what about a lawyer?
Hey pussy, you're gonna get cancer and AIDS and DIE PUSSY!
Fuck yeah!
This fucking nasty ass shit away, bro.
Ugh, bro, I'm gonna throw the fuck up, bro.
Ugh, bro!
Ugh, dude.
Fuck is this, dude.
Fuck this is, bro.
Ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh.
Dude, I need to just don't hold the scene. I know fucking cat
Fuck that hey pussy you saw fucking call me bitch
You live with your fucking dad, bro. You're a fucking bitch, bro. Fuck you
William went bro. You live with your fucking daddy bro in your fucking dad's house, bro
This dude's girlfriend doesn't even fucking live nowhere near him, bro.
Look, the pussy's calling me, dude.
Hey, what's up, pussy?
Hey, what's up, bitch?
Shut the fuck up!
Watch what I'm in for, you fucking pussy!
Fuck you!
Fucking pussy.
This is a fucking bitch, dude!
Bitch-ass motherfucker!
Call back bitch!
Hey, what's up you fucking fanboy hey fanboy hey fanboy
Hey, fanboy. Hey, fanboy shut the fuck up your fucking pedophile
Shut your pedophile ass up motherfucker
You're a fucking pedophile, bro. You're a fucking pedophile shut the fuck up
Shut the fuck up. You're a fucking pedophile bitch you fucking rape kid
Fuck you pedophile motherfuckers you fucking faggot
Fuck you, bro. I don't give a fuck dude
Fuck you, bro
I'm gonna go talk to my 15 year old girlfriend guys. Can I hurt everybody?
You know
Literally gonna go talk to my 15 year old girlfriend guys. Good night guys
I'm gonna go talk to my 15 year old girlfriend, bro
my 12-year-old girlfriend right now.
Bye.
Bye, guys.
Stop hitting that fucking dog.
You just hit that dog with a fucking rock, dude.
What's up? Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Come here right here.
Come on here. Come on here.
Come here.
Yeah, you scared bitch.
You scared bitch.
This is not cool at all. This is not what you caught
Dude, please please please you are going to die
You are going to die dude. You are going to die stop
You're going to die you are going to die
We're here
No, how old are you? Oh my god, dude, she looks like she's 15. They're beautiful
You have a boyfriend or what? Yeah, you do
Bro that 15 year old was cute
She looks like one
It's not going to look all stupid, you know what I'm saying?
Me and you act stupid, right?
Or do you want me to act stupid?
I want you to stop messing around, all right?
Okay.
Go sit over there, man.
He's English?
Okay.
Who's this guy over here?
Uh, I just seen him, uh, he came over here and he started banging on this person's, uh, door.
I'm just going to check and make sure you guys have weapons.
Hey, bro, what are you trying to do?
Hold on, let me just check and make sure you got no weapons on you, all right?
Okay.
Okay, guys.
Brandon?
Yeah.
Okay.
How much should we have to drink today?
10 drinks, beers, liquor, what are we talking about?
Liquor? What type of liquor?
I can't get that, but what type? Whiskey, tequila?
We're going to set you in here, okay? Alright, go ahead and step inside.
Watch your step. Watch your step.
Stop doing that yo dude stop doing that that's not appropriate
I'm going to drink this and then I'm going to have the whole stream bro.
I'm gonna drink this and then I'm ending the whole fucking stream, bro. Fuck this shit, bro
Let him tuck tail and turn and run. Hey gamble. Hey did the ex bro. I fuck I own you bro
How does it feel that I own you bro? Like I said, bro
go have a baby bro like I said bro go have a baby bro your girlfriend her
uterus is cursed go have a baby bro go do it go get married go get married bro
I was on his nuts or whatever he played me like a fiddle played me like a fiddle
I was talking about how my dad used to build saltwater aquariums bro this dude
goes all out studying and researching bro so he could build his own saltwater
aquarium bro clown bro you're a clown bro
You're a clown bro, and now you're gonna go through all this because of Anita bro
I was gonna leave you alone bro despite you threatening my mom bro. I was gonna let let it slide bro
I'm telling you bro. I was gonna let everything slide bro. I'm about to end this bro. Good night guys
I see it's one of those nights that
I'm outie bro. I'm out of here, bro. I'm out of here guys. Good night Q army. Good night
Everybody I need to go talk to somebody dude. All right guys. Good night later everybody
Ooh, what am I supposed to do?
I have to press it.
Is it fun to press?
Can we share something?
Can we share like a...
Okay.
Oh yeah, whatever you want to do.
I have to know what to do now.
I'm on my, whatever you're on, bro.
What am I on?
I'm a zombie, bro.
I'm a zombie?
Yeah, because I answer how much it's going to cost?
Oh, don't come to a restaurant and act like that, bro.
That's how you can act.
I'm always going to-
Yeah, you're totally right, yeah.
Well, yeah, you're always going to-
I'm going to call my dad and say something.
I'm on my-
Whatever you're on, bro.
What am I on?
I'm a zombie, bro.
there's just annoying bro because people are trying to work dude and you're
like a hallowed annoying person bro like people don't care dude like all the
shit you say and want to ask and shit you want to be a streamer
niger sit down niger sit the fuck down wait wait what the fuck are you doing to me sit down wait
sit down and we're gonna choke you and we're gonna make the bull that
Brandon please please Brandon please what please stop don't abuse me don't abuse me
don't abuse me dude
wait wait what what the fuck are you talking about what the fuck you don't
know I don't want your cock bro I don't know what you're talking about don't
let's go walk you know no no no no no no let's go get water no let's get water
Get your phone right now, and let's go get some drinks
We need some Gatorades, and we need some stuff to make sure that you're okay, bro
No, it's not about ah
It's not about ah
We're supposed to be fucking homies, dude. We're supposed to pick each other up whenever we when whenever the
message calls us no it's not about that it's not about that bro you're not
supposed to be doing all these drugs you're not supposed to be doing all
these drugs and you're not supposed to be doing all this shit bro you make you
make you look sad
I wanna suck on a 17 year old pussy, dude. Straight boner, dude. Straight fucker. Put 7 year old pussy.
I want Gamble to get married bro and have a daughter, dude. I want you to, bro.
Then you'll see what a PDF is, bro. I'll show you then, I'll show you PDF.
I'm gonna go talk to my 12 year old girlfriend right now. Bye.
Is my asshole pretty spread open or what?
You wanna fuck me in the ass or what, Gamble?
Yeah, and of course you're striking. Well, go ahead. It's not your not your video
You're gonna strike me for for doing that. Okay, you on the you on the you on the footage
Or you just have that video posted
Not always your video. Okay. It's unlisted on your channel. Okay
Well, you're gonna be fast